ask4pc.net 2016-09-22

# Privacy policy ~ Ask4pc: Free Software Solutions, Serial keys, Keygen , Cracks Direct Download

_**What information do we collect?**_

We collect information from you when you fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 _ **What do we use your information for?**_

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

; To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

_**How do we protect your information?**_

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

_**Do we use cookies?**_

We do not use cookies , but some advertisers on our site may use it.  
Technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices

 _ **Third party links**_

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 _ **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**_

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 _ **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**_

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 _ **Sources**_

This site may contain links and matters from external sources. All those materials are of their respective owner only. We respect them and do not possess any right over them. If anyone have any issues please contact us.

 _ **Online Privacy Policy Only**_

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 _ **Your Consent**_

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 _ **Changes to our Privacy Policy**_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 16-01-2014

 _ **Contacting Us**_

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.ask4pc.net  
Contact@ask4pc.net

This policy is powered by Trust Guard, your [PCI compliance](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm) authority.
